<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liam Power</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liam Power</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:49:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GPU Hash Tables For Fast Voxel Retrieval</title>
      <link>/posts/voxel-gpu-hashing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 08:49:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/voxel-gpu-hashing/</guid>
      <description>Augmenting Sparse Voxel Octrees with GPU-friendly hashtables to give constant lookup times for voxel attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cv</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 13:27:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Vitae This is my CV, with some personal data (phone number, etc.) elided. If you&#39;re interested in these details, please get in touch via email.  Work Experience    Ericsson Aug 2020 &amp;ndash; Present  Software Engineer    Worked on a large, complex cloud-native telecom system related to next-gen 5G mobile networks. Worked to optimise performance event streaming for 5G baseband, as well as implementing a secure TLS layer over this event stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 10:22:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code/</guid>
      <description>My Projects This page lists some of the software projects that I&#39;ve worked on. My GitLab profile contains the source code for most of these projects, as well as plenty of odds and ends that I didn&#39;t think were interesting enough to go here.
 Sabre A Sparse Voxel Octree voxel renderer written for my University Final Year project. Written in C++ and using modern OpenGL. The software can import and voxelise GLTF mesh files to a high level of detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned to Program: Ten Years On</title>
      <link>/posts/ten-years-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ten-years-programming/</guid>
      <description>Reflections on how I learned to program computers, ten years after I first began</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
